>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Speaking of inheritance,
如果我们想用原型来做一个真正的孩子课
if we wanted to do a true sort of
child class in the prototypal style,
我们会定义 8 线和另一个车间的卡车司机
we'd define line eight and
another workshop contructor.
我们再做一次工作坊的方式
And the way we make
another workshop extend or
从工作坊继承的是这条线抱歉
inherit from the workshop is this
line right here, oops, sorry.
这条线，第 11 行，对象点创建。
This line right here,
line 11, object dot create.
在第 11 行目标点创建
On line 11, object dot create,
我们是在说我刚开始的原型，不是我想要的，
we are saying take the prototype that I
initially got, which is not what I want,
以及将其链接到的位置，以确保它链接到研讨会点原型。
and change where it is linked to make sure
that it links the workshop dot prototype.
对象点创建有两个内容。
Object dot create does two things.
它是一个内置在 es5 中的实用程序，它做了两件事情。
It's a utility built in the es5 and
it does two things.
看看这听起来很熟悉吧
See if this sounds familiar.
对象点创建的第一个方法是创建全新的空
The first thing that object dot create
does is create a brand new empty
薄空气的对象点。
object dot of thin air.
然后，它所做的第二件事就是把它链接到另一个物体上。
And then, the second thing it does is
it links that object to another object.
这是新算法的前两个步骤
It's the first two steps
of the new algorithm
称为对象点创建的特定 API 方法。
as a specific API method
called object dot create.
所以我们说我要另一个车间的样机
So here, we're saying I want my
another workshop prototype to
与车间的原型相关的原型。
be prototype linked to
the workshop do prototype.
或者，再一次，它是一个反模式，但是
Alternatively, again,
it's a bit of an anti pattern, but
或者你可以说另一个车间点的样机
alternatively, you could have said
another workshop dot prototype
dot dunderproto 等于车间点原型。
dot dunderproto equals
workshop dot prototype.
你可以把它改造好
You could have rewired it that way.
但是我们正在创建一个新对象来获取新的链接。
But we're creating a new
object to get a new linkage.
这就是我所看到的最近几个 js 的对象
And that is the effect, then,
that the js recent parts object that I've
在第 16 行创建，该对象链接到原型对象，
created on line 16, that object is
linked to the prototype object,
它链接到研讨会点原型对象。
which is linked to the workshop
dot prototype object.
它们通过隐藏的原型链联系起来。
They're linked through that
hidden prototype chain.
>> Kyle Simpson: 现在，这些对象之间存在链接，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, the linkage
that exists between these objects,
这并不是一件坏事
that's not a bad thing at all.
这其实是一个神奇的神奇的东西。
That's actually a magical awesome thing.
但我们有一整群的复杂性在上面。
But we have a whole bunch of
complexity layered on top.
我们有这些看起来像构造函数的东西。
We've got all these things that
look like constructor functions.
我们都有这个详细的点样机
We've got all this verbose
dot prototype stuff.
我们发现了新的关键词
We've got confusing new keyword instances.
所有这些建筑都是在这三大对象上连接在一起的。
And all of this artifice is on top of
these three objects linked together.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 其实是把物体联系在一起
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And it's the objects
being linked together that actually
创造了所有的力量
creates all of the power here.
它创造了我的能力，让我说第 18 条 js 最近的部件点说起来。
It creates the ability for me to say
line 18 js recent parts dot speak up.
那个对象有说话的方法吗
Does that object have
a speak up method on it?
此处的第 18 行是关于 JSRecentParts的对话方法吗 ?
The line here, line 18, is there
a speak up method on JSRecentParts?
>> 扬声器 2: 否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那么接下来呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So where does it go next?
>> 演讲者 2: 另一个研讨会?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Another workshop?
>> Kyle Simpson: 它转至另一个研讨会原型
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It goes to
another workshop prototype
有话想说
which does have a speak up.
因此，当调用该函数时， thisKeyword 将指向什么 ?
So when that function is invoked,
what is the thisKeyword gonna point at?
>> 演讲者 3: JSRecentParts。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: JSRecentParts.
>> Kyle Simpson: 仍将指向 JSRecentParts。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Still gonna
point to JSRecentParts.
上面写着这个圆点
And it says this dot ask.
JSRecentParts 是否有一个请求方法?
So does JSRecentParts have an ask method?
那它要去哪
So where's it gonna go?
备份到另一个车间原型。
Backup to another workshop prototype.
那个有个问法吗
Does that one have an ask method on it?
那它要去哪
So where's it gonna go?
这个有个问法吗
Does this one have an ask method on it?
是，当它调用时，此关键字将指向什么 ?
Yes, when it invokes,
what's the this keyword gonna point at?
还会指向 JSRecentParts。
Still gonna point at JSRecentParts.
不管你有多少次的样机链你要决心找到你的
No matter how many times up the prototype
chain you have to resolve to find your
方法，不管它们有多大的程度，
methods, and no matter how far up they go,
此绑定仍由调用站点在 root 用户控制。
the this binding is still controlled
at the root by the call site.
我有个很棒的学术术语我叫它超级独角兽魔术
And I have a fancy academic term for
that, I call that super unicorn magic.
太神奇了能在这些功能中找到这些功能
That's amazing and awesome that it
can find these functions in all these
在原型链中的不同位置，并确保它们的上下文
different places in the prototype chain,
and still make sure their this context
正是我们所期望的，它根植于调用堆栈。
is exactly what we would expect,
which is rooted at the call stack.
你有问题吗
You had a question?
>> 扬声器 4: 仅确认。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Just to absolutely confirm.
如果第 11 行不存在，那么这将中断，因为另一个车间点
Were line 11 not to exist, this would
break because another workshop dot
原型只会指向对象点原型。
prototype would just point
to object dot prototype.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是正确的，对。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is correct, yes.
如果您愿意，第 11 行是扩展条款。
Line 11 is the extends clause,
if you will.
这就是我们如何把另一个车间与车间联系起来的。
That's how we make another
workshop link to workshop.